[{"answer": "I think it's dreadfully serious for Rupert Murdoch, and his family and his company.", "docId": "110718pmt", "aSentId": 32, "question": "And as Rupert Murdoch prepares to address members of parliament in Britain tomorrow, how serious is this moment for him and his company?", "qSentId": 31}, {"answer": "Well, I'm sure that the editors would be asking those question.", "docId": "110718pmt", "aSentId": 51, "question": "Why weren't they asking those questions?", "qSentId": 50}, {"answer": "No, I would not.", "docId": "110718pmt", "aSentId": 57, "question": "I mean would you expect him to?", "qSentId": 56}, {"answer": "Let's turn to Porter Bibb here.", "docId": "110718pmt", "aSentId": 65, "question": "I would expect he might have asked the question, how -- how are we getting all of this wonderful stuff?", "qSentId": 64}, {"answer": "Well, he's got to address several constituencies on this issue.", "docId": "110718pmt", "aSentId": 72, "question": "Is the newspaper division for him now in Britain simply not making enough money to make it worth saving in a crisis like this?", "qSentId": 71}, {"answer": "No, I mean, we have no idea.", "docId": "110718pmt", "aSentId": 84, "question": "Was your information that the Murdochs were considering selling their newspaper division?", "qSentId": 83}, {"answer": "Well, I mean, there's clearly an I affinity for newspapers by Rupert Murdoch.", "docId": "110718pmt", "aSentId": 97, "question": "Do you see a time coming as newspapers diminish in their importance, when the Murdoch's Corporation, News Corporation, with or without the Murdochs, Views newspapers as disposable assets to let them focus on television and movies, which make more money?", "qSentId": 96}, {"answer": "OHEN: Yes, News Corp has lost over $8 billion of value since the crisis erupted in the last few weeks.", "docId": "110718pmt", "aSentId": 106, "question": "Do you think that these shares are now undervalued, given the scale of this crisis?", "qSentId": 105}, {"answer": "I think he's probably led a race to the bottom.", "docId": "110718pmt", "aSentId": 118, "question": "I mean again, looking at him dispassionately, do you think he's been primarily a force for good or a force for not so good in the media?", "qSentId": 117}, {"answer": "There's two distinctions here.", "docId": "110718pmt", "aSentId": 125, "question": "And in terms of exposure to the American part of the company, am I right in thinking that if that is proven, if there were bribes being paid, either anonymously or in fake names, or whatever it may be, if it were paid by News International, a British company, does that still impact on the American part of the business?", "qSentId": 124}, {"answer": "Well, I think you have to separate the questions.", "docId": "110718pmt", "aSentId": 134, "question": "Or do you worry conversely that all this attention on this means there may be further attacks on freedom of the press?", "qSentId": 133}, {"answer": "Well, you know, Piers, I just got a call an hour ago, and Rupert wanted to tell me personally that you know he's not OK.", "docId": "110718pmt", "aSentId": 161, "question": "How are they dealing with this, do you think?", "qSentId": 160}, {"answer": "I think he will be -- I mean the one thing about Rupert is that -- yes, he can be ruthless, but actually we can just talk about this -- I think one -- he's ruthless, but also entrepreneurial.", "docId": "110718pmt", "aSentId": 210, "question": "How do you think he will deal with this?", "qSentId": 209}, {"answer": "Well, Piers, number one, thank you for having me.", "docId": "110718pmt", "aSentId": 252, "question": "So what do you think went wrong here?", "qSentId": 251}, {"answer": "OK.", "docId": "110718pmt", "aSentId": 325, "question": "Why?", "qSentId": 324}, {"answer": "Well, I felt a huge disappointment.", "docId": "110718pmt", "aSentId": 373, "question": "What did you feel when you watched those images?", "qSentId": 372}, {"answer": "Of course she should lead the life she wants to lead.", "docId": "110718pmt", "aSentId": 391, "question": "Or should she be allowed to lead the life she wants to lead?", "qSentId": 390}, {"answer": "It means that public opinion had been driven I think by the saturation coverage on television and all of the commentary, so that most people were directed to believe -- and, you know, I'm sure you wouldn't deny the fact you were directing people to think this -- that this woman killed her child.", "docId": "110718pmt", "aSentId": 421, "question": "What does that mean?", "qSentId": 420}, {"answer": "Tell me about the -- I also love the fact that even then you could tell that you had this kind of fire brand attitude.", "docId": "110718pmt", "aSentId": 446, "question": "Jealous?", "qSentId": 445}, {"answer": "You know, Piers, it's so complicated.", "docId": "110718pmt", "aSentId": 469, "question": "Was it as simple as that?", "qSentId": 468}, {"answer": "Oh, Piers, come on, you've been through this, I'm sure.", "docId": "110718pmt", "aSentId": 515, "question": "When you get criticized, what do you think is the biggest misconception about you?", "qSentId": 514}]